{
    "id": "9bd7c625371e4a9498f4e388567e26b5",
    "title": "Idiomatic Expressions Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………………. you have completed the work, you can go home.",
            "description": "Now that can mean as a result of the fact",
            "answers": [
                "As that",
                "Now that",
                "So that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e430cc6dd793434795b164b9cabbca59"
        },
        {
            "question": "People dislike communalism and all that it ………………………...",
            "description": "To stand for is to represent. ",
            "answers": [
                "stands up",
                "stands for",
                "stands out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a5725970a8c049bbbb0797b66601f3ee"
        },
        {
            "question": "They had to ……………………… many difficulties during their journey.",
            "description": "To put up with is to tolerate or endure. ",
            "answers": [
                "put off with",
                "put down with",
                "put up with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "72c4d5fe8fd54fe289281bc17de10828"
        },
        {
            "question": "While I was looking for a book, I ………………………. this old photograph.",
            "description": "To come across is to find or meet accidentally. ",
            "answers": [
                "came across",
                "came off",
                "came up with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "72e850abded24b88999cb3fccadebe88"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must ………………………. the challenge.",
            "description": "To take up a challenge is to accept it. ",
            "answers": [
                "take out",
                "take on",
                "take up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ee845198b8cc4bbba89852400ced1d26"
        },
        {
            "question": "Did you ……………………… that story or is it true?",
            "description": "To make up is to invent.",
            "answers": [
                "make off",
                "make up",
                "make out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fde5de55517c40cebc0e7a4917a035ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has ………………………. enough money for his daughter’s marriage.",
            "description": "To put by is to save. ",
            "answers": [
                "put off",
                "put by",
                "put up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cc847d50e20f4a1fb3155359874f104e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He didn’t …………………………..",
            "description": "To turn up is to come. ",
            "answers": [
                "turn out",
                "turn up",
                "turn off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "17068044667243f487345b91d8b636fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "The tyrant ………………………… all opposition.",
            "description": "To put down is to suppress. ",
            "answers": [
                "put off",
                "put out",
                "put down"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "75e592f0f0584c59ac096dac639119ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is only through experience that we ………………………… our shortcomings.",
            "description": "To come to terms with is to accept. ",
            "answers": [
                "come to terms with",
                "get to terms with",
                "keep pace with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "adcca9efaf52452a8039a0eac9c1f15d"
        },
        {
            "question": "We all ……………………… him.",
            "description": "To look up to somebody is to have great respect for them.",
            "answers": [
                "look up to",
                "look to",
                "look up"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1062c05a01964c12ba701d50a806efaa"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher ………………………… the students to work hard.",
            "description": "To call upon is to exhort. ",
            "answers": [
                "called in",
                "called upon",
                "called out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6685e40bf4ce4f33b72e33a02dc1706c"
        }
    ]
}